<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gem Hunt</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">291723887929785</string>
    <string name="twitter_consumer_key">MlQ64bSR3I3nFPE2zY9tZe47r</string>
    <string name="twitter_consumer_secret">fxUQRJnYxPCbauKcjoeLtesIAXRQ8IfOv0nywlMPBV8kTMqh2e</string>
    <string name="username_hint">Username</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="password_action_label">Sign in</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_hint">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="team_name_hint">Team Name</string>
    <string name="first_name_hint">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name_hint">Last Name</string>
    <string name="register_button_text">Register</string>
    <string name="code_hint">Code</string>
    <string name="team_tracker_delete_text">Delete</string>
    <string name="team_tracker_edit_text">Edit</string>
    <string name="congratulations_title">Congratulations</string>
    <string name="completed_hunt_text">You have successfully completed the treasure hunt!</string>
    <string name="team_tracker_team_name_hint">Team Name</string>
    <string name="team_tracker_team_code_hint">Team Code</string>
    <string name="team_tracker_starting_location_index_hint">Starting Location Index</string>
    <string name="edit_treasure_hunt_title_hint">Treasure Hunt Title</string>
    <string name="edit_treasure_hunt_date_hint">Date to set Active</string>
    <string name="register_phone_number_hint">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="register_email_address_text">Email Address</string>
    <string name="tracking_permission_text">During the app, the admin will be able to monitor your progress through the treasure hunt.
        \n\nThis will involve the admin being able to track your current location, your location data will be wiped from the database once you logout of the app.
        \n\nThey will no longer be able to track you after this point. Do you agree to allow the admin to use your location data?</string>

    <string name="text_with_paragraphs1">
        The team tracker is where all of the participating teams and their progress are listed.
        \n\nHere, you can edit and manage all participating teams.
    </string>
    <string name="text_with_paragraphs2">
        To delete multiple teams at once, simply press SELECT and select the teams you wish to delete.
        \n\nThen press DELETE.
    </string>
    <string name="t3">
        To add a new team, select ADD TEAM and fill in the relevant information.

    </string>
    <string name="t4">
        The admin map tracks the location of all teams in addition to the locations of all gems that are to found.
        \n\nThe small blue circles represent the participating teams.
        \n\nThe purple gems indicate where the unfound treasure lies.

    </string>

    <string name="t5">
        By pressing \'management\', you are able to see the current treasure hunts that have been made and are taking place.

    </string>

    <string name="t6">
        To create a treasure hunt, simply press CREATE NEW TREASURE HUNT and provide a title and the date you would like the hunt to go live.
        \n\nThen select ADD.
    </string>
    <string name="t7">
        To be able to add treasure hunt locations, hold down where you would like to place the a new gem location.
    </string>
    <string name="t8">
      Provide the location with a title, an index and a short description.
    </string>
    <string name="t9">
      To edit a gem location, hold down the gem you would like to edit and change the information as desired.
    </string>
    <string name="t10">
      On the management page, you can view the QR codes assigned to each treasure hunt.
        \n\nHold down one of the treasure hunts, and you will be presented with the option to edit a hunt, view its QR codes or delete it.
    </string>
    <string name="t11">
      If you select QR Codes, you will be able to see the names of that treasure hunt\'s gem locations and view their QR codes.
    </string>
    <string name="team_tracker_preferences_text">Preferences</string>


</resources>
